And this lesson will implement the functionality behind the Disconnect button.
We'll start off here and abduct James, and under the document ready function, we'll make another on
click function.
So let's copy this one right here.
And pace below.
And change it to disconnect, why fine?
And change the function name to disconnect by phone.
All right, so copy this function.
And let's go down to the bottom of the file.
And now let's make a comment.
Disconnects swipe five.
Once the disconnect button is pressed.
And reloads the Web page.
And it's a function.
Disconnect wi fi.
And here will use Ajax.
And for the Irwell, it's forward slash Wi-Fi disconnect, Jason.
And the data type.
This, Jason.
And the method.
Is delete.
This false.
Data.
Is timestamp.
Data now.
Now at a semicolon.
And here will update the Web page.
And use set timeout.
And just follow me here.
Location, don't reload.
Is true with a semicolon inside.
Then comma, and let's set the page to reload after 20 milliseconds.
OK.
So when the disconnect button is pressed, this function is invoked and it refreshes the page after
two seconds.
Meanwhile, in the web server side, Wi-Fi is disconnected and that'll be implemented in the a handler.
All right, so let's implement that now and head over to HTP, Server does see.
So we'll start by copying this your eye handler information.
And let's reuse it below.
And first, let's change this to Wi-Fi disconnect.
That, Jason.
And the structure name to Wi-Fi disconnect.
And the urine.
Is Wi-Fi disconnect, Jason?
The method is HTP delete.
And the handler, it's HTP server, Wi-Fi disconnect.
Jason Handler.
OK, so let's pass the structure name to register that you are a handler.
And let's go up and define it.
Now, let's copy this comment.
And it.
And change this to Wi-Fi disconnect, Jason.
And we'll say responds by sending a message to the wife by application to disconnect.
Then let's grab the name.
Copy it.
And now say static espérer tape, let's drop the name and its age http request type pointer.
Ari Kim.
And now S.P. log.
Why fi disconnect, Jason requested?
In next year's wi fi apps and message.
And we'll say here, wi fi message.
User requested state disconnect.
And will define that later.
Now, let's just return ESP, OK?
Next, let's copy this.
And we'll create a message in the Wi-Fi app.
So go to Wi-Fi app Dunwich.
And let's just drop it right here.
OK, now let's head over to the message handling section of the see file.
And now let's copy this case message.
And pasted here.
And first, let's remove this, and now let's update the case to message user requested stay disconnect.
And now let's update the log message as well.
And now here will update the global retry number.
And we'll set it to Max Connection Retrace.
Because we don't want to re attempt to connection when the disconnect button is pressed.
OK, so next we're going to call the disconnect function, which will result in the case below and then
the failed message to be sent to the web server and we'll need to adjust our state machine here to compensate
for this later.
For now, let's just continue.
And that's espero check.
ESP Wi-Fi disconnect.
And now let's change the Ogbe led status to.
Our GB led FTP server started.
OK, so I'm not sure if this name makes sense anymore, so I'll just make a comment for you or to do.
To rename this status leaded to a name more meaningful.
Or to your liking.
So it might be a good idea to change it if you like.
For now, let's just build the project.
And once you flesh it.
Now, connect to the ESPN.
Then now I'll head over to the Web page.
And now, actually, we want to open the monitor.
And also, I did this backwards, so don't do it this way.
You'll want to do the monitor first, then go to the web page.
Because now I'll probably have to reload the Web page.
So let me do that.
And then I'll just make sure I'm connected.
OK.
And now we're back, OK?
So let's connect, you know, the password.
And connect.
All right, good, so now let's reload to test it.
OK, so now let's disconnect.
Nice.
The Page Reloaded and the Connect info is cleared, and we're no longer connected to an access point.
Excellent.
Great.
So let's continue our development in the next lesson.